A Finding Aid to the Dore Ashton Papers, 1849, 1931-2010 in the Archives of American Art AAA.ashtdore
Archives of American Art
- Research files, 1849, 1950-1984, 2009, undated; 4; 3.3 Linear feet Boxes 7-10, ov 15-16
  - Exhibition: "Abstract Art Before Columbus", 1956-1959 (Box 8, Folder 45-46)
  - Exhibition: "Abstract Drawings and Watercolors: U.S.A.", 1961-1965 (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - Exhibition: Darmstadt Drawings International, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - Exhibition: "Lam, Gorky, Noguchi, Matta in New York: 1939-1949", 2009, undated (Box 8, Folder 49)
  - Exhibition: "Modern American Drawings", 1965-1966 (Box 8, Folder 50)
  - Exhibition: "Poets and Prints", 1960 (Box 8, Folder 51)
  - Individuals: Milton Avery, 1967-1968 (Box 8, Folder 52)
  - Individuals: Rene Berger, 1967-1968 (Box 8, Folder 53-54)
  - Individuals: Jacopo Luis Borges, 1967-1976 (Box 9, Folder 1-2)
  - Individuals: Pol Bury, 1953-1969 (Box 9, Folder 3-4)
  - Individuals: Milton Cohen, 1960-1964 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Individuals: James Ensor, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Individuals: John Ferren, 1979-1980 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Individuals: Helen Frankenthaler, 1960-1965 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Individuals: Ernest Gambart, undated (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Individuals: Allan Kaprow, 1961-1968 (Box 9, Folder 10-11)
  - Individuals: Andrew Mikhailovich Lanskoy, 1955 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Individuals: Jack Levine, 1952, undated (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Individuals: Richard Lindner, 1969-1977 (Box 9, Folder 14-16)
  - Individuals: Gustav Moreau, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 17-18)
  - Individuals: Seong Moy, 1951-1954 (Box 9, Folder 19-21)
  - Individuals: Constantino Nivola, 1955-1964 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Individuals: Gabor Peterdi, 1952, undated (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Individuals: Rainer Marie Rilke, 1974, undated (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Individuals: Miriam Schapiro, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Individuals: Nicolas Schoffer, 1954-1955 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Individuals: Tony Smith, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Individuals: Jean Tinguely, 1959-1962 (Box 9, Folder 28-31)
  - Individuals: Mark Tobey, 1953-1971 (Box 9, Folder 32-36)
  - Individuals: Jack Tworkov, 1957-1961 (Box 9, Folder 37-40)
  - Individuals: Adja Yunkers, 1950-1953 (Box 9, Folder 41-44)
  - Topics: Angry Arts, 1964-1971 (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - Topics: Association Internationale des Critiques D'Art, 1963, undated (Box 9, Folder 46-48)
  - Topics: Black Art, 1966-1969 (Box 9, Folder 49-50)
  - Topics: Chile, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 51)
  - Topics: Civil Rights, 1963-1964 (Box 9, Folder 52)
  - Topics: Coinciding Arts, 1960-1968 (Box 9, Folder 53-54)
  - Topics: Czech Art, 1957-1962 (Box 9, Folder 55)
  - Topics: Dadaism and Neo-Realism, 1960-1964 (Box 9, Folder 56-57)
  - Topics: Dadaism and Neo-Realism, 1960-1964 (Box 10, Folder 1-2)
  - Topics: Film, 1964-1970 (Box 10, Folder 3-4)
  - Topics: Fondation Maeght, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 5-7)
  - Topics: MOMA: Dissidents in Art, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 8-10)
  - Topics: New York Times, 1958-1964 (Box 10, Folder 11-13)
  - Topics: P.E.N. American Center, 1980, undated (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Topics: Performing Arts, 1967-1968 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Topics: Poetry, 1973-1978, undated (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Topics: Polish Art, 1960-1961 (Box 10, Folder 17-19)
  - Topics: Printmaking, 1958-1953 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Topics: Prints, 1955-1964 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Topics: Religious Art, 1951-1962 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Topics: Rio Grande Graphics, 1952, undated (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Topics: Symbolism, 1951-1964 (Box 10, Folder 24-26)
  - Topics: Washington Post, 1963-1981 (Box 10, Folder 27)
- Printed Materials, 1931-1981, undated; 5; 0.5 Linear feet Box 10
  Arranged alphabetically by type of material, chronologically thereafter
  Printed materials collected by Ashton include brochures and booklets, clippings, exhibition announcements and catalogs, galley proofs, press releases and programs. Topics include Dubuffet, Avedon, Ippolito, the New York School, collecting, Italian art, Jackson Pollock, sculpture, book reviews, and lectures.
  - Brochures and Booklets, 1951-1969, undated (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Clippings, undated (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Clippings, 1931-1935 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Clippings, 1951-1952 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Clippings, 1953 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Clippings, 1954 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Clippings, 1955 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Clippings, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Clippings, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Clippings, 1958 (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Clippings, 1960-1962 (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Clippings, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Clippings, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - Clippings, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - Clippings, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - Clippings, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - Clippings, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - Clippings, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 45)
  - Clippings, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 46)
  - Clippings, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 47)
  - Clippings, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 48)
  - Clippings, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 49)
  - Clippings, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 50)
  - Clippings, 1975-1976 (Box 10, Folder 51)
  - Clippings, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 52)
  - Clippings, 1979-1980 (Box 10, Folder 53)
  - Clippings, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 54)
  - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, 1933-1979, undated (Box 10, Folder 55)
  - Galley Proofs, circa 1964-1970 (Box 10, Folder 56)
  - Press Releases, 1962-1978 (Box 10, Folder 57)
  - Programs, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 58)
- Artwork, 1949, 1953, 1982, undated; 6; 0.1 Linear feet Box 10, ov 15
  Arranged in donor's original order
  Artwork includes various designs of a face and symbols on nine scraps of waxy paper; a Christmas card possibly designed by Adja Yunkers; 4.25x5.75 print signed Lichtenstein 1949; pencil or charcoal on paper design, dated Jan 23.52 marked "for Dore," illegible signature; collage print on paper entitled "Dore on the Beach," signed Adja Yunkers, with envelop from the Edna Hibel Gallery in New York.
  - Drawings and Prints, 1949, 1952, 1983, undated (Box 10, Folder 59)
- Photographs of Artwork, circa 1950-2010; 7; 2.5 Linear feet Boxes 10-14, ov 15
  Arranged alphabetically by artist's surname, followed by subjects
  Series 7 contains black and white photocopy prints and a few prints and postcards, acquired by Ashton for reference, and representing mostly 19th and 20th century American and European artists. Most are labeled and of a single work of art, some show artworks in exhibition spaces.
  - A, circa 1950-2010 (Box 10, Folder 60)
  - Adams, Pat, circa 1950-2010 (Box 10, Folder 61)
  - Afro, circa 1950-2010 (Box 10, Folder 62)
  - Alechinsky, Pierre, circa 1950-2010 (Box 10, Folder 63)
  - Antes, Horst, circa 1950-2010 (Box 10, Folder 64)
  - Appel, Karel, circa 1950-2010 (Box 10, Folder 65)
  - Arakawa, circa 1950-2010 (Box 10, Folder 66)
  - Arp, Jean, circa 1950-2010 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Avery, Milton, circa 1950-2010 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - B, circa 1950-2010 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Bacon, Francis, circa 1950-2010 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Baldessari, John, circa 1950-2010 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Barragan, Luis, circa 1950-2010 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Baruchello, circa 1950-2010 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Bearden, Romare, circa 1950-2010 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Beauchamp, Robert, circa 1950-2010 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Beck, Rosemarie, circa 1950-2010 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Beckmann, Max, circa 1950-2010 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Bess, Forrest, circa 1950-2010 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Birolli, Renato, circa 1950-2010 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Bladen, Ronald, circa 1950-2010 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Boghosian, Varusan, circa 1950-2010 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Bonnard, Pierre, circa 1950-2010 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Brancusi, Constantin, circa 1950-2010 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Braque, Georges, circa 1950-2010 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Brooks, James, circa 1950-2010 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Bucker, Robert, circa 1950-2010 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Burne-Jones, Edward Coley, circa 1950-2010 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Bury, Pol, circa 1950-2010 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - C, circa 1950-2010 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Caro, Anthony, circa 1950-2010 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Carone, Nicholas, circa 1950-2010 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Cesar, circa 1950-2010 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Cezanne, circa 1950-2010 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Chamberlain, John, circa 1950-2010 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Christo, circa 1950-2010 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Corneille, circa 1950-2010 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Corot, circa 1950-2010 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - D, circa 1950-2010 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - D'Arcangelo, Allen, circa 1950-2010 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Davie, Alan, circa 1950-2010 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Davis, Stuart, circa 1950-2010 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - de Chirico, Giorgio, circa 1950-2010 (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Degas, Edgar, circa 1950-2010 (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - de Kooning, Willem, circa 1950-2010 (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Delauney, Robert, circa 1950-2010 (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - Demuth, Charles, circa 1950-2010 (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - de Rivera, Jose, circa 1950-2010 (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - Diebenkorn, Richard, circa 1950-2010 (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - Dine, circa 1950-2010 (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - Donati, Enrico, circa 1950-2010 (Box 11, Folder 44)
  - Dorazio, circa 1950-2010 (Box 11, Folder 45)
  - Dubuffet, Jean, circa 1950-2010 (Box 11, Folder 46)
  - Duchamp, Marcel, circa 1950-2010 (Box 11, Folder 47)
  - Dufour, Bernard, circa 1950-2010 (Box 11, Folder 48)
  - Dugmore, Edward, circa 1950-2010 (Box 11, Folder 49)
  - E, circa 1950-2010 (Box 11, Folder 50)
  - Engel, Jules, circa 1950-2010 (Box 11, Folder 51)
  - F, circa 1950-2010 (Box 11, Folder 52)
  - G, circa 1950-2010 (Box 11, Folder 53)
  - Gauguin, Paul, circa 1950-2010 (Box 11, Folder 54)
  - Geoffrey, Iqbal, circa 1950-2010 (Box 11, Folder 55)
  - George, Herbert, circa 1950-2010 (Box 11, Folder 56)
  - Giacometti, Alberto, circa 1950-2010 (Box 11, Folder 57)
  - Glarner, Fritz, circa 1950-2010 (Box 11, Folder 58)
  - Glasco, Joseph, circa 1950-2010 (Box 11, Folder 59)
  - Gleizes, Albert, circa 1950-2010 (Box 11, Folder 60)
  - Goldberg, Michael, circa 1950-2010 (Box 11, Folder 61)
  - Goodnough, Robert, circa 1950-2010 (Box 11, Folder 62)
  - Gorky, Arshile, circa 1950-2010 (Box 11, Folder 63)
  - Gottlieb, Adolph, circa 1950-2010 (Box 11, Folder 64)
  - Goya, circa 1950-2010 (Box 11, Folder 65)
  - Graham, John, circa 1950-2010 (Box 11, Folder 66)
  - Greene, Stephen, circa 1950-2010 (Box 11, Folder 67)
  - Grosz, George, circa 1950-2010 (Box 11, Folder 68)
  - H, circa 1950-2010 (Box 11, Folder 69)
  - Haber, circa 1950-2010 (Box 11, Folder 70)
  - Hadzi, Dimitri, circa 1950-2010 (Box 11, Folder 71)
  - Hajdu, Etienne, circa 1950-2010 (Box 11, Folder 72)
  - Hartigan, Grace, circa 1950-2010 (Box 11, Folder 73)
  - Hartley, Marsden, circa 1950-2010 (Box 11, Folder 74)
  - Held, Al, circa 1950-2010 (Box 11, Folder 75)
  - Hepworth, Barbara, circa 1950-2010 (Box 11, Folder 76)
  - Higgins, Eduard, circa 1950-2010 (Box 11, Folder 77)
  - Hofmann, Hans, circa 1950-2010 (Box 11, Folder 78)
  - Holtz, Carl, circa 1950-2010 (Box 11, Folder 79)
  - Hultberg, John, circa 1950-2010 (Box 11, Folder 80)
  - I, circa 1950-2010 (Box 11, Folder 81)
  - Indiana, Robert, circa 1950-2010 (Box 11, Folder 82)
  - Inokuma, circa 1950-2010 (Box 11, Folder 83)
  - Ipousteguy, Jean, circa 1950-2010 (Box 11, Folder 84)
  - Ippolito, Angelo, circa 1950-2010 (Box 11, Folder 85)
  - J, circa 1950-2010 (Box 11, Folder 86)
  - Jacobsen, circa 1950-2010 (Box 11, Folder 87)
  - Jewish Museum New York, circa 1950-2010 (Box 11, Folder 88)
  - Johns, Jasper, circa 1950-2010 (Box 11, Folder 89)
  - Johnson, Lester, circa 1950-2010 (Box 11, Folder 90)
  - Johnson, Ray, circa 1950-2010 (Box 11, Folder 91)
  - K, circa 1950-2010 (Box 11, Folder 92)
  - Kelly, Ellsworth, circa 1950-2010 (Box 11, Folder 93)
  - Kienbush, William, circa 1950-2010 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Klapheck, circa 1950-2010 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Klee, Paul, circa 1950-2010 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Klein, Yves, circa 1950-2010 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Kleine, Franz, circa 1950-2010 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Koenig, J.F., circa 1950-2010 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Kohn, Wolf, circa 1950-2010 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Kupka, Frank, circa 1950-2010 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - L, circa 1950-2010 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Lanyon, Peter, circa 1950-2010 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Lasansky, Mauricio, circa 1950-2010 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Leger, Fernand, circa 1950-2010 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Liberman, Alexander, circa 1950-2010 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Lipchitz, Jacques, circa 1950-2010 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Lipton, Seymour, circa 1950-2010 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Lobdell, Frank, circa 1950-2010 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Louis, Morris, circa 1950-2010 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Lukin, Sven, circa 1950-2010 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - M, circa 1950-2010 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Marca-Relli, Corrado, circa 1950-2010 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Magritte, Rene, circa 1950-2010 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Maillol, Aristide, circa 1950-2010 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Marin, John, circa 1950-2010 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Matisse, Henri, circa 1950-2010 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Matta, circa 1950-2010 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Maurer, Alfred, circa 1950-2010 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - McNiell, George, circa 1950-2010 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Miro, Joan, circa 1950-2010 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Mitchell, Joan, circa 1950-2010 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Modigliani, Amadeo, circa 1950-2010 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Mondrian, Piet, circa 1950-2010 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Monet, Claude, circa 1950-2010 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Moore, Henry, circa 1950-2010 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Motherwell, Robert, circa 1950-2010 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Moy, Seong, circa 1950-2010 (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Muller, Robert, circa 1950-2010 (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Munch, Edvard, circa 1950-2010 (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - Murray, Robert, circa 1950-2010 (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - N, circa 1950-2010 (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - Nakian, Reuben, circa 1950-2010 (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - Natkin, Robert, circa 1950-2010 (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - Nevelson, Louise, circa 1950-2010 (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - Newman, Barnett, circa 1950-2010 (Box 12, Folder 43)
  - Nivola, Constantino, circa 1950-2010 (Box 12, Folder 44)
  - Noland, Kenneth, circa 1950-2010 (Box 12, Folder 45)
  - O, circa 1950-2010 (Box 12, Folder 46)
  - O'Keeffe, Georgia, circa 1950-2010 (Box 12, Folder 47)
  - Oldenburg, Claes, circa 1950-2010 (Box 12, Folder 48)
  - Oliveira, Nathan, circa 1950-2010 (Box 12, Folder 49)
  - Oran, Ran, circa 1950-2010 (Box 12, Folder 50)
  - Ortman, George, circa 1950-2010 (Box 12, Folder 51)
  - P, circa 1950-2010 (Box 12, Folder 52)
  - Paolozzi, Eduardo, circa 1950-2010 (Box 12, Folder 53)
  - Paris, Harold, circa 1950-2010 (Box 12, Folder 54)
  - Pearlstein, Philip, circa 1950-2010 (Box 12, Folder 55)
  - Picasso, Pablo, circa 1950-2010 (Box 12, Folder 56)
  - Pissarro, Camille, circa 1950-2010 (Box 12, Folder 57)
  - Pollock, Jackson, circa 1950-2010 (Box 12, Folder 58)
  - Quaytman, Harvey, circa 1950-2010 (Box 12, Folder 59)
  - R, circa 1950-2010 (Box 12, Folder 60)
  - Rauschenberg, Robert, circa 1950-2010 (Box 12, Folder 61)
  - Remington, Deborah, circa 1950-2010 (Box 12, Folder 62)
  - Richenberg, Robert, circa 1950-2010 (Box 12, Folder 63)
  - Riopelle, Jean, circa 1950-2010 (Box 12, Folder 64)
  - Rodin, Auguste, circa 1950-2010 (Box 12, Folder 65)
  - Rosati, James, circa 1950-2010 (Box 12, Folder 66)
  - Rosenthal, Bernard, circa 1950-2010 (Box 12, Folder 67)
  - Roszak, Theodore J., circa 1950-2010 (Box 12, Folder 68)
  - Roth, Frank, circa 1950-2010 (Box 12, Folder 69)
  - Rothko, Mark, circa 1950-2010 (Box 12, Folder 70)
  - S, circa 1950-2010 (Box 12, Folder 71)
  - Saul, Peter, circa 1950-2010 (Box 12, Folder 72)
  - Schapiro, Miriam, circa 1950-2010 (Box 12, Folder 73)
  - Schoffer, Nicolas, circa 1950-2010 (Box 12, Folder 74)
  - Schwitters, Kurt, circa 1950-2010 (Box 12, Folder 75)
  - Scott, William, circa 1950-2010 (Box 12, Folder 76)
  - Seurat, Georges, circa 1950-2010 (Box 12, Folder 77)
  - Sima, Joseph, circa 1950-2010 (Box 12, Folder 78)
  - Smith, Leon Polk, circa 1950-2010 (Box 12, Folder 79)
  - Smith, Richard, circa 1950-2010 (Box 12, Folder 80)
  - Soulages, Pierre, circa 1950-2010 (Box 12, Folder 81)
  - Stamos, Theodoros, circa 1950-2010 (Box 12, Folder 82)
  - Stankiewicz, Richard, circa 1950-2010 (Box 12, Folder 83)
  - Stefanelli, Joseph, circa 1950-2010 (Box 12, Folder 84)
  - Steinberg, Saul, circa 1950-2010 (Box 12, Folder 85)
  - Stella, Frank, circa 1950-2010 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Sterne, Hedda, circa 1950-2010 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Still, Clyfford, circa 1950-2010 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - T, circa 1950-2010 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Tal Coat, Pierre, circa 1950-2010 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Tapies, Antoni, circa 1950-2010 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Tobey, Mark, circa 1950-2010 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Tomlin, Bradley Walker, circa 1950-2010 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Torres-Garcia, Joaquin, circa 1950-2010 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Turnbull, William, circa 1950-2010 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Turner, Joseph Mallord William, circa 1950-2010 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Tworkov, Jack, circa 1950-2010 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - V, circa 1950-2010 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Vasarely, Victor, circa 1950-2010 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Vicente, Esteban, circa 1950-2010 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Villon, Jacques, circa 1950-2010 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Viseux, Claude, circa 1950-2010 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Voulkos, Peter, circa 1950-2010 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - W, circa 1950-2010 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Wiley, William, circa 1950-2010 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Xceron, Jean, circa 1950-2010 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Yrisarry, Mario, circa 1950-2010 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Youngerman, Jack, circa 1950-2010 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Z, circa 1950-2010 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Zacharias, Athos, circa 1950-2010 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Zox, Larry, circa 1950-2010 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - American 19th Century Drawing and Painting: Bierstadt-Tarbell, circa 1950-2010 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - American 19th Century Drawings and Paintings - Sargent, John Singer, circa 1950-2010 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - American 19th Century Drawing and Painting - Whistler, James McNeill, circa 1950-2010 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - American 20th Century Drawings, circa 1950-2010 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - California and Chicago Artists, circa 1950-2010 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Environmental Earthworks, John Gibson Gallery, circa 1950-2010 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - European 19th and 20th Century Sculpture: A-D, circa 1950-2010 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - European 19th and 20th Century Sculpture: J-M, circa 1950-2010 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - European 19th and 20th Century Sculpture: Picasso, Pablo, circa 1950-2010 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - European 20th Century Painting, circa 1950-2010 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Japanese 20th Century Painting, circa 1950-2010 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous Photographers: Hammid, Hine, Kertesz, Lartigue, Moore, Steichen, circa 1950-2010 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous, circa 1950-2010 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - 20th Century Drawings, circa 1950-2010 (Box 14, Folder 11)